good afternoon welcome to my grading two
下午好，欢迎来到我的二年级
modules the sequel two modules in one
将续集模块分为两个模块
lesson I guess I lied it wasn't really
一课，我想我撒谎不是
one lesson well it was it was an
一课好，那是
introductory lesson but there it is so
入门课程，但确实如此
how many so many people that saw that
有多少人看到了
session this morning okay good that'll
今天早上的会议，好的，那会
help a bit but I'll try to make this
有点帮助，但我会尽力做到这一点
relatively independent so this is
相对独立，所以这是
another live coding session I will make
我将进行另一个现场编码会议
mistakes please shout them out if you
错误请大声喊出来，如果你
think you can help questions of
认为您可以帮助解决以下问题
clarification are welcome during the
欢迎在此期间进行澄清
main part but deeper questions let's try
主要部分，但更深层次的问题让我们尝试
and hold those for the end please so
并坚持到底
what we're gonna do here is look at a
我们在这里要做的是看一个
little application a slightly bigger
小应用稍大
application then we look at this morning
应用程序，那么我们今天早上看
I've got JDK 9 here build 180 181 the GA
我在这里有JDK 9 build 180181 GA
version or take this little application
版本或采用此小应用程序
that we're gonna do - we're gonna do two
我们要去做-我们要去做两个
things first we're gonna modularize it
首先，我们要对其进行模块化
from the top down now this application
从上到下现在这个应用程序
uses some popular but as yet unmonitored
使用一些流行但尚未监控的内容
libraries and will show how you can
库，并说明如何
modular eyes a little app even before
模块化的眼睛甚至一个小应用程序
it's dependencies have been modularized
它的依赖关系已经模块化
by their maintainer
由他们的维护者
then we'll do the opposite thing we'll
然后我们会做相反的事情
go back to just having a regular
回到有规律的
classpath application and we'll modular
类路径应用程序，我们将进行模块化
eyes its dependencies we'll pretend that
看着它的依赖关系，我们会假装
we're the maintainer z' of these
我们是这些的维护者
libraries we'll modularize those and
我们将这些库模块化
we'll show how that works with the class
我们将展示如何与全班一起使用
battle application then finally at the
战斗应用，然后终于在
end we'll wind up with an actual fully
最后，我们将以实际完全
modular eyes application so first things
模块化的眼睛应用程序，所以第一件事
first right rather rather than doing a
优先，而不是先做
boring boring old hello world I thought
我以为无聊的无聊的旧世界
I'd do something a little bit a little
我会做点事
bit richer here so I've got a file here
这里有点丰富，所以我这里有一个文件
of tweets in JSON format you know the
JSON格式的推文，您知道
XML of a 21st century it's well maybe a
21世纪的XML也许是
little more readable than XML I'm not
比XML更具可读性，我不是
sure
当然
so let's write write a little app to
所以我们写一个小应用程序来
display these in a more readable format
以更易读的格式显示这些
now we don't have to write it because
现在我们不必写它了，因为
I've already got it or tweet some is the
我已经知道了，或者发了一些推文
name of the app it's got a main Clyde
该应用的名称，其中包含一个主克莱德
it's got two classes unlike this
有两堂课与此不同
morning's app it's got two I've got two
早上的应用程序有两个我有两个
classes let's take a look I've got a
课让我们看一看
main class it uses the Jackson XML sorry
主类使用Jackson XML对不起
the Jackson JSON data binding library
Jackson JSON数据绑定库
you know this is very simple I create
你知道我创建的这很简单
that creates an object mapper makes a
创建对象映射器的对象
list of tweets reading from system input
从系统输入读取的推文列表
and then displays those tweets on
然后在上面显示这些推文
standard output in it and it uses this
标准输出，它使用此
tweet class nearby little poder up
在附近的小微博上发推文
represents a tweet it's using a single
表示一条推文，它使用单个
timestamp to represent the time using
时间戳代表使用
more Jackson's stuff we've got to
我们必须去的更多杰克逊的东西
annotate annotated properties a
注释属性a
timestamp property and the text property
时间戳属性和文本属性
which is just the text
这只是文字
all right so that's pretty simple let's
好吧，那很简单，让我们
compile it and and just show that it
编译并显示它
works before we attempt to change
在我们尝试改变之前有效
anything in my Lib directory I've got
我的Lib目录中的所有内容
Jackson the 3:3 Jackson jar files that I
我的杰克逊3：3杰克逊jar文件
need these are these are slightly old
需要这些是这些有点老
version but for these purposes it
版本，但出于这些目的
doesn't really matter let's compile
没关系，让我们编译
these so what do we do the Java C - D
这些，所以我们该怎么做Java C-D
classes class let's see if they're live
让我们看看他们是否还活着
Jackson and it start with core data bind
杰克逊，它开始于核心数据绑定
live Jackson annotations and I'll just
现场杰克逊注释，我只是
find everything I can and compile it a
找到我能做的一切并将其编译
lot right now let's make a jar file
现在很多，让我们制作一个jar文件
and this is all very mundane that is one
这都是非常平凡的
of the loudest fun buzzers I've ever
我见过的最响亮的有趣蜂鸣器
heard
听过
okay and just to show that everything
好，只是为了证明一切
works we can we can run it at that long
工作，我们可以这么长时间运行
awful classpath add my my tweet some guy
糟糕的classpath将我的tweet添加到了一些家伙
and what do we get
那我们得到什么
there we go tweets the tweets in a more
在那儿，我们在更多的地方发推文
readable format okay
可读格式好
woohoo that's our that that's our
woohoo是我们的那是我们的
starting point so let's start by
起点，所以让我们开始
modularizing tweets um here's the
模块化推文，嗯，这是
structure again just to remind you what
再次构造只是为了提醒您什么
we're going to do is we're going to put
我们要做的就是放
a module declaration in the org dot
组织点中的模块声明
tweets um directory
推特um目录
module or tweets um and now in a module
模块或推文um，现在在模块中
I need to declare what my module exports
我需要声明模块导出的内容
and what it requires so this this is a
以及它需要什么，所以这是一个
little application module it doesn't
小应用程序模块
export any API so there aren't gonna be
导出任何API，因此不会
any exports in it right
任何出口都可以
but code in this module uses the JAXA
但是此模块中的代码使用JAXA
those three Jackson libraries but but
那三个杰克逊图书馆，但是
what do i do how do i what I do here
我该怎么办我该怎么办
what I'd like to write is Jackson core
我想写的是杰克逊的核心
or you know calm down faster XML
或者您知道冷静一点XML
something or but I don't actually have a
某些东西，但是我实际上没有
Jackson core module all I've got is is a
我仅有的Jackson核心模块是一个
Jackson core jar file and the same for
杰克逊核心jar文件与
the other Jackson libraries that are
其他的杰克逊图书馆
sitting there so I mean the the things
坐在那里所以我的意思是
in plain old RAR files they aren't
在普通的旧RAR文件中，它们不是
modules right there's no there's no
模块没有就没有
module info in those now I could go and
现在我可以去那些模块信息了
edit those jar files and sort of force
编辑这些jar文件并进行排序
module infos in modules and fatah class
模块和法塔赫类中的模块信息
files into them but that's probably not
文件放入其中，但这可能不是
a good a good idea it's generally never
一个好主意，这通常是从来没有
a good idea in this with jar files
这个用jar文件的好主意
provided by someone else so the answer
由别人提供，所以答案
here is a feature in jigsaw called
这是拼图中的一个功能，称为
automatic modules so an automatic module
自动模块，所以自动模块
is way of taking a relatively sane jar
是拿一个比较理智的罐子的方法
file or set a relatively sane jar files
文件或设置相对健全的jar文件
and just treating them as modules even
甚至将它们视为模块
though they don't have module infant
虽然他们没有模块婴儿
class files in them this is for for
其中的类文件用于
top-down migration it requires a couple
自上而下的迁移需要几个
of things above all those jar files for
在所有这些jar文件中，
example they can't have conflicting
例子，他们不能有冲突
packages so there have conflicting
包，所以有冲突
packages you have to leave them on a
包，你必须把它们放在一个
class path but Jackson is a well
上班路，但杰克逊是个好
engineered system and there there aren't
工程系统，没有
conflicting packages so that's not a
有冲突的软件包，所以这不是
problem with automatic modules the name
自动模块的名称问题
of the module is taken from the name of
模块的名称取自
the jar file which is probably not the
jar文件可能不是
actual name of the actual name that the
实际名称
that module will be given by its
该模块将由其
maintainer when its maintainer gets
维护者得到维护者时
around to it so this is why in top-down
因此，这就是为什么自上而下
migration we recommend that if you're if
迁移时，我们建议您
you're using things as automatic modules
您正在使用事物作为自动模块
don't
别
publish your own module because you'll
发布您自己的模块，因为您将
be declaring dependencies on something
声明对某事的依赖
that might have a different name when
在以下情况下可能具有不同的名称
its maintainer actually want module
它的维护者实际上需要模块
arises it anyway for two but for
无论如何都会出现两个
top-down migration this is pretty good
自上而下的迁移，这相当不错
heuristic if you're just doing models on
启发式，如果你只是在做模型
your own for now until your dependencies
直到您的依赖为止
have caught up so at this point I can
已经赶上了，所以在这一点上我可以
write it requires Jackson Core requires
写它需要杰克逊核心要求
Jackson data deveined requires Jackson
公布的杰克逊数据需要杰克逊
notation set annotation or annotations
注释集注释
annotations and that should work right
注释，应该正确
that is a really loud phone buzzer it's
那是一个非常响亮的电话蜂鸣器
gonna be on the recording so there's a
会在唱片上，所以有一个
there's another way to figure out what
还有另一种方法来弄清楚
what things your existing code might
您现有的代码可能会做什么
need and that's with the Jade EPS tool
需求，这就是Jade EPS工具
that I mentioned at the keynote
我在主题演讲中提到的
yesterday so Jade EPS is kind of a Swiss
昨天，所以Jade EPS有点像瑞士人
Army knife of static analysis for for
军刀的静态分析
code that runs on top of the JDK just as
在JDK上运行的代码
a side note very important one is the
旁注非常重要的一个是
JDK internals option you can you run
您可以运行的JDK内部选项
with this option that will look at an
使用此选项，将查看
existing jar file or seven jar files and
现有的jar文件或七个jar文件，以及
see if there any uses of JDK and
看看是否有使用JDK和
journals and happily there are no uses
日记，很高兴没有用
of JDK internal api's in our little
JDK内部api的介绍
application okay so that's good you can
应用程序还可以，这样很好
also you can also use this - s option
您也可以使用此-s选项
we'll show you some more that not found
我们将向您展示更多未找到的内容
is because I need to tell it where to
是因为我需要告诉它去哪里
find the rest of the dependencies here
在这里找到其余的依赖项
so let me copy
所以让我复制
that so J tips we'll look at all of this
因此，J技巧我们将研究所有这些
stuff now we see that Jade EPS is saying
现在，我们看到Jade EPS在说
that there's code and Ord tweet some jar
有代码，而Ord鸣叫一些罐子
that is gonna want stew use things in
那就是要炖用的东西
these Jackson jar files and that'll
这些杰克逊的jar文件，
probably work as if you treat them as
可能就像您将它们视为
automatic moms it's also telling us it
自动妈妈也告诉我们
noticed what we forgot that or tweet
注意到我们忘记了或发了什么
some jar is using using that timestamp
一些罐子正在使用该时间戳记
class in the Java sequel module so we
Java续集模块中的类，因此我们
forgot that and we need to add that here
忘记了，我们需要在这里添加
requires Java not sequel otherwise it
需要Java不续集，否则
won't compile and certainly won't run
将不会编译，当然也不会运行
all right so we've got our our
好吧，所以我们有我们的
modularized application here let's
模块化应用程序让我们
remove that and compile it we're gonna
删除并编译它，我们将
compile first two mods directory the
编译前两个mod目录
modular form of classes directory module
类目录模块的模块化形式
path Lib we tell the compiler modules
路径库我们告诉编译器模块
source path
源路径
source Java C is a Java C has a deep
Java C的源代码是Java C有很深的
understanding of the structure of a
对一个结构的理解
source tree so you can structure a
源代码树，因此您可以构建一个
source tree as with with with per module
与每个模块一起使用的源代码树
directories and just tell it go compile
目录，然后告诉它进行编译
the tweets and module and and it'll just
推文和模块，它只会
grab the whole thing you don't have to
抓住你不需要的全部东西
list individual Java source files by
列出单个Java源文件
yourself whoops model that you gotta
你自己的模特，你必须
type it right mark there we go now in
键入正确的标记，我们现在进入
our mods directory we've got out as an
我们的mods目录我们作为一个
exploded exploded module we can job a
爆炸爆炸模块，我们可以工作
pea
豌豆
there's our compiled module info as it
有我们的编译模块信息
has exactly what we expect in it ok
完全符合我们的期望
let's create a jar file for that here
让我们在这里为此创建一个jar文件
we're gonna take it
我们要接受
from there and we're gonna put it in the
从那里，我们要把它放在
Lib directory and along the way let's
lib目录，一路走来
add it let's add a main class when you
添加它，让我们在您添加主类时
package up a modular jar or even a non
包装一个模块化的罐子，甚至没有
modular jar for that matter you can
模块化的罐子，你可以
specify the main class the entry point
指定主类的切入点
for it and we're just gonna say as a
为此，我们只是要说
convenience that the the main class is
主要类是
in is org tweets in tweets um main yep
in是org主推文中的org tweets
that should work there we go the
应该在那里工作，我们去了
marginal modular tweets um jar file and
边际模块化推文um jar文件和
now we can run it we're gonna run it
现在我们可以运行它，我们将运行它
with
与
the module path is live so remember in
模块路径是活动的，因此请记住
live we now have we have our jackson
生活，我们现在有我们的杰克逊
annotation jar files an unchanged
注解jar文件保持不变
they have just downloaded from maven
他们刚刚从Maven下载
central and the tweet some jar file that
中央和鸣叫一些罐子文件
we just built will say java module path
我们刚刚构建的将说Java模块路径
lib and ask it to run tweet some
lib并要求它运行鸣叫一些
application and we get an exception oh
申请，我们得到一个例外哦
no what happened
没事
what happened was we missed something
发生了什么事我们错过了什么
when we modular eyes so let's take a
当我们将眼睛模块化时，让我们
look at the exception java.lang reflect
看一下java.lang的异常反映
inaccessible object exception unable to
无法访问的对象异常无法
make org tweet some tweet accessible
使组织推文可访问一些推文
module word tweet some does not open org
模块词鸣叫一些无法打开组织
to tweet some to module jackson dot data
鸣叫一些模块杰克逊点数据
bind so basically what's going on here
因此基本上绑定这里发生了什么
the Jackson data binding library like
Jackson数据绑定库
most data binding libraries is using
大多数数据绑定库正在使用
reflection to dig in to the POJO class
反思POJO类
that it's trying to support and that's
它正在努力支持，那就是
not working that's not working because
不工作，那是行不通的，因为
the module declaration for the tweet
鸣叫的模块声明
some module doesn't make it available
某些模块无法使用
it's you know it's an internal package
你知道这是一个内部包装
but in this case it's not quite totally
但这种情况并不完全
internal because well as the author of
内部的，因为以及
the tweets and module ID I know I'm
我知道我的推文和模块ID
using Jackson data binding it's okay for
使用Jackson数据绑定可以
Jackson data binding to access the guts
Jackson数据绑定以访问胆量
of my of my internal class I actually
我的内部班级中，我实际上
want it to do that now what I could do
想要它现在做我能做的
is exports like a I mean I could try
是像我一样的出口我可以尝试
exports or tweet zone I've tried it a
出口或推特区，我已经尝试过了
try to export that package that might
尝试导出可能会
work but I'm sorry actually that won't
工作，但我很抱歉实际上不会
work I misspoke so let's see what
工作我误会了，让我们看看
happens I'm gonna use a little little
碰巧我要用一点点
command a clicked up called Jada @jj to
命令一个名为Jada @jj的点击
save some time so let's let's recompile
节省一些时间，让我们重新编译
and repackage
并重新包装
our module and try to run it again so I
我们的模块并尝试再次运行它，所以我
mean
意思
[Music]
[音乐]
sorry
抱歉
thank you
谢谢
live coding is always a bit of a
实时编码总是有点
high-wire act all right let's try this
高压线好吧，让我们尝试一下
again and what's gonna happen the same
再一次，会发生什么一样
thing happens and the reason the same
事情发生了，原因相同
thing happens is that when you export a
发生的事情是，当您导出一个
package that does not make all of its
不能完全包装的包装
all of its non-public members available
其所有非公开成员都可用
for deep reflection it makes them
为了深层思考，这使他们
available available as an API so so
可作为API使用，因此
other code can can use the exported API
其他代码可以使用导出的API
of that package what we need really need
该包中我们真正需要的
to do is what that error message
要做的是那个错误信息
originally suggested which is something
最初建议这是什么
other than export there's this other way
除了出口以外，还有其他方式
to expose a package and that's called
暴露一个包装，这叫做
opens so opens is designed exactly for
打开，因此打开是专门为
this kind of use case you have a package
这种用例你有一个包装
it's got some classes in it you don't
它有一些课程，你没有
intend that package to be an API you
打算将该软件包用作API
don't want other code other codes and
不需要其他代码和其他代码
other modules or elsewhere to compile
其他模块或其他要编译的模块
against it but you do want to allow
反对它，但你确实想允许
something like a data binding binding
类似于数据绑定绑定
library to use deep reflection on it so
库在其上使用深层反射
basically you can think of it at a high
基本上你可以想到它
level it's it's it's exporting out at
水平是它在出口
compile time only at runtime and at
仅在运行时和在
runtime allow reflection on non public
运行时允许对非公共进行反思
members of the types of Av of even non
非偶数类型的成员
public types did you a quick question
公开类型是您的一个快速问题
indeed I can if I if I want to be a
的确可以，如果我想成为一个
little bit paranoid I can say open zorg
有点偏执我可以说打开zorg
tweets m2 jackson data bind this is
鸣叫m2杰克逊数据绑定这是
called a qualify and qualified open that
称为合格和合格公开赛
you can also do qualified exports if you
您也可以进行合格的出口
want to export something just to one
想要将某物导出到一个
other module or set of modules to have
其他模块或一组模块
you know an even higher level of
你知道更高的水平
integrity in your system
系统的完整性
okay so let's JJ that guy up again and
好吧，让我们再JJ那个家伙起来，
now it works okay so now we've got the
现在可以了，所以现在我们有了
modular application it's using the
使用的模块化应用程序
Jackson libraries as automatic modules
杰克逊图书馆作为自动模块
and we're done with the first step okay
第一步就完成了
tip it take to get make a click you get
提示获得点击所需的费用
a little bit of a closer look let's make
让我们仔细看一下
a little JRE so we can we can see what's
一点JRE，所以我们可以看到什么
going on I'm just gonna run j-link real
继续，我只是要运行j-link real
quick here so I list the modules in this
在这里快速，所以我在此列出模块
in this Jerry it's got just the modules
在这个Jerry中，只有模块
that this application needs
该应用程序需要的
we're gonna can run it don't need don't
我们将可以运行它，不需要，不需要
need all those modules in the JDK all
全部需要JDK中的所有那些模块
70-odd of them there there's some some
其中有70多个
into some good options in the Java
Java中的一些不错的选择
launcher now for diagnosing the module
现在用于诊断模块的启动器
system you can do show module resolution
系统可以显示模块分辨率
and it will display information as the
它将显示信息为
resolver works to figure out what
解析器会找出原因
modules you need so it starts with the
您需要的模块，因此从
the root module in this case for the
在这种情况下，根模块
resolution process is the tweet some
解决过程是鸣叫一些
module it sees tweet some requires
它看到的模块鸣叫一些要求
sequel requires Jackson data bind it
续集需要Jackson数据绑定它
shows you the URLs at which it finds
向您显示找到它的URL
those in the case of the sequel module
那些在续集模块的情况下
that's in the the jrt URL that's or the
在或的jrt网址中
internal nya virtual file system in
内部的Nya虚拟文件系统位于
which you can find all the classes
您可以找到所有课程
inside the JDK finds annotations finds
在JDK中查找注释
core down here figures out that's sequel
这里的核心是续集
oh yeah that means logging and sequel
哦，是的，这意味着记录和续集
requires xml binds up some services and
需要xml绑定一些服务，并且
then goes so that's that's what's going
然后就是这样
on there that is a really allowed phone
那里是一个真正允许的电话
those are I I'm just sorry sorry that's
这些是我，我很抱歉，对不起
a door okay
一扇门还好
so automatic modules are they're good
所以自动模块是很好的
for modular izing applications as I said
我说过用于模块化应用程序
top-down but they're but they're not
自上而下，但它们不是
recommended for use in published
建议用于已发布
libraries now there there is yet another
图书馆现在在那里
kind of intermediate step here Monta
蒙塔的中间步骤
lysing existing libraries can can can
可以溶解现有的图书馆可以
sometimes they take a fair bit of work
有时他们需要做很多工作
in order to enable the maintainer x' of
为了使维护者x'
existing libraries to kind of set a
现有库来设置
stake in the ground you know declared
押在你知道宣告的土地上
this part of the frontier as the module
这部分边界作为模块
name they intend to use when they get
他们打算在使用时使用的名字
around to doing proper modular ization
进行适当的模块化
we've we provided an interim step you
我们提供了一个临时步骤
can use a new entry in the jar file
可以在jar文件中使用新条目
manifest called automatic module name if
清单被称为自动模块名称，如果
that entry is there and your jar file is
那个条目在那里，你的jar文件是
not an actual module then the module
不是实际的模块，而是模块
system will read that manifest attribute
系统将读取清单属性
and use that as the name of the
并将其用作
automatic module that will be created
将创建的自动模块
for your jar file so today it's a kind
为您的jar文件，所以今天是一种
of an intermediate weight way point
中等重量航点的
along the way to modular is
一直到模块化
and I've been pleased to see a number of
我很高兴看到一些
popular libraries where their maintainer
热门图书馆，其维护者
is already declared automatic module
已经声明为自动模块
names in advance of doing the work to
在工作之前先命名
actually figure out what should be in
真正弄清楚应该在里面
their module declarations and publishing
他们的模块声明和发布
them as as actual modules so so that's
它们作为实际模块，所以
great
大
okay let's rewind here I'm gonna clean
好吧，让我们在这里倒带，我会很干净
up everything let me leave that for the
一切都让我留给
moment and through the wonders of
时刻，并通过奇观
mercurial I'm going to now enter an
Mercurial我现在要输入
alternate universe in which I pretend to
我假装的替代宇宙
be one of the maintainer z' of the
成为...的维护者z'之一
Jackson libraries so let's recompile the
杰克逊图书馆，让我们重新编译
tweet some application as a regular old
将某些应用程序发布为普通旧版本
whoops
哎呀
classpath application
类路径应用
that should do the trick okay
应该可以解决的
there we go I non-modular jar file so
我们去了我的非模块化jar文件，所以
that's that's how we're gonna operate
这就是我们要运作的方式
without actually if we go let's do
如果没有，我们去吧
now just true music okay that'll make
现在只要是真正的音乐就可以了
things a little easier later on okay so
事情以后再容易一点，所以
we imagine we are the main dangers of
我们以为我们是
the Jackson libraries we've got these
杰克逊图书馆，我们有这些
source trees here for Jackson itself you
这里是杰克逊本人的源代码树
know calm down pastor mxml Jackson core
知道冷静下来牧师MXML杰克逊核心
blah blah blah all these all these
等等等等所有这些
wonderful classifier Java source files
精彩的分类器Java源文件
then it's licensed and so forth so this
然后它已获得许可，依此类推
could be a biggish project what you know
你知道的可能是一个很大的项目
there's that there's a lot of stuff here
这里有很多东西
how do we go about it so the directory
我们如何去做，所以目录
structure actually tells us a fair
结构实际上告诉我们一个公平
amount you can kind of guess well you
你可以猜测的数量
know annotations is probably you know
知道注释可能是您知道的
each one of these does each one of these
这些中的每一项都执行这些中的一项
jar files does is you know it kind of
jar文件是吗，您知道吗
looks like a model a bit of a module
看起来像模型有点模块
already but how do we figure out what
已经，但是我们如何找出
you know what they export what they
你知道他们出口什么
require what they what they what they
要求他们什么他们什么他们
need and again we have J Depp's comes to
需要再一次让我们有德普（J Depp）
the rescue
营救
so we run J Depp's on those Jackson jar
所以我们在那些杰克逊罐子上运行J Depp
files we have still in the Lib directory
我们仍然在Lib目录中的文件
and Jade ups this does that same static
和翡翠ups这样做相同的静态
analysis that I showed before and shows
我之前显示并显示的分析
what the relationships are so all of any
关系到底是什么
of these jar files need you know the
这些jar文件需要您知道
base module well everybody needs the
基本模块以及每个人都需要
base module data bind uses sequel an XML
基本模块数据绑定使用XML续集
and also uses the other two Jackson jar
并使用另外两个杰克逊罐
files
档案
so Jay Depp's has yet another option
所以杰伊德普（Jay Depp's）还有另一种选择
remember I did say Swiss Army knife
记得我说过瑞士军刀
jaidev's can generate module info draft
jaidev可以生成模块信息草稿
module info Java files for you so I'll
模块信息Java文件供您使用，我将
do generate module info into a directory
确实将模块信息生成到目录中
called evil into my source directory
称邪恶为我的源目录
this is a little bit scary I'm using a
这有点吓人我正在使用
tool and it's gonna write into my source
工具，它将写入我的源代码
tree okay that's that's alright it'll be
树好吧那没关系
okay
好的
let's do Lib Jackson core first okay so
首先让我们做库伯·杰克逊的核心，好吧
we have a module info it's always a good
我们有一个模块信息，它总是一个很好的
idea to look at what it did here and
看看它在这里做了什么的主意，
we've got jackson core exports a bunch
我们有杰克逊核心出口一堆
of packages okay and oh what's this hmm
好的包装，哦，这是什么
this says provides what what is all
这说提供了什么
about so it turns out the module system
大约是原来的模块系统
knows about services so services are a
了解服务，因此服务是
fundamental tool in the model system
模型系统中的基本工具
they're especially useful for breaking
它们对于破坏特别有用
cyclic dependencies when you might think
您可能会想到的循环依赖性
that to mod to modules each need to
修改为每个模块都需要
depend depend on the other or through
依靠对方或通过
some more complicated kind of cyclic
一些更复杂的循环
relationship the answer more often than
关系答案比
not will be refactor one of them as a
不会将其中之一重构为
service that the other one looks up and
另一个查找的服务
that will help you break that cycle we
这将帮助您打破这一周期，我们
use we've sort of used services
使用我们的二手服务
throughout the JDK itself to break many
整个JDK本身打破了许多
cycles along the way here
在这里骑行
okay so I can actually generate module
好吧，所以我实际上可以生成模块
infos for all of these at once it does
所有这些的即时信息
all three so that Corwin looks pretty
这三个让Corwin看起来很漂亮
good I probably ought to change the
好，我可能应该改变
module name to you know calm Doster XML
您知道的模块名称平静的Doster XML
dot whatever but I'll just leave that
点点什么，但我就离开
here for now for simplicity let's look
为了简单起见，现在来看
at the annotations module info check
在注释模块信息检查中
that out okay it's just going to export
没关系，它只是要出口
one package that looks all right data
一包看起来不错的数据
bind module info so a couple of things
绑定模块信息，所以有几件事
here one is we see there's it put
这是我们看到的
requires in here and in particular it
在这里特别是要求
put in these requires transitive
放在这些需要传递
declarations so when one module requires
声明，因此当一个模块需要时
another that just means that the for the
另一个只是意味着
first module we'll be able to access the
第一个模块，我们将能够访问
exported or or open packages of that
出口或打开包装
other module if yeah you know some third
其他模块，如果是的，你知道第三点
module requires the first one it's not
模块需要第一个不是
gonna see sorry the second one sorry if
要第二次见到对不起，如果
this is getting get to become it if if
如果，如果
if module if module a requires B and B&amp;B
如果模块，如果模块a需要B和B＆B
exports and packages then module a can
导出并打包然后打包一个罐
use the exported packages in B if some
如果有的话，使用B中导出的软件包
third module X requires a it will see
第三个模块X需要一个它将看到的
the exported packages of a but it won't
的导出包，但不会
necessarily won't see the exported
一定看不到导出
packages of B unless X also requires B
B的包装，除非X也需要B
but if a uses X in its own api's then as
但是如果a在自己的api中使用X，则
a convenience to users like like module
方便用户使用的模块
X it should do it requires transitive
X它应该这样做需要传递
and it provides the convenience
它提供了便利
basically means any module that requires
基本上是指任何需要
Jackson data bind will implicitly also
Jackson数据绑定也会隐式地
require Jackson annotations and Jackson
需要Jackson注释和Jackson
core and Java sequel and java xml and j
核心和Java续集以及Java xml和j
depth data has a heuristic for figuring
深度数据具有启发性
this out by analyzing the type
通过分析类型
signatures of public public classes and
公共公共课的签名和
interfaces okay so those are the
接口好，所以这些是
requires that have generated
要求已经产生
and it also generated a bunch of exports
它也产生了一堆出口
based on the X the package that exists
基于X存在的包
now Jade EPS has no way of figuring out
现在，Jade EPS无法确定
what might be internal and why not there
什么可能是内部的，为什么不在那里
are various conventions people have used
人们使用过的各种约定
over the years for marking things
多年来标记事物
internal but in this case we can pretty
内部的，但在这种情况下，我们可以
easily see there are some imple packages
容易看到有一些简单的软件包
so we're just gonna comment those out or
所以我们只是要评论那些或
heck let's just delete them because
嘿，让我们删除它们，因为
chances are pretty good that that's not
很有可能不是
meant to be part of the Jackson API so
打算成为Jackson API的一部分，因此
we don't need them and there's another
我们不需要它们，还有另一个
service here than J tips figured that
这里的服务比J提示想的要
out by looking at the at the services
通过查看服务
directory in meta F okay so we've done
Meta F中的目录，好了，我们已经完成了
all that let's compile and we're going
所有这些让我们编译，我们将继续
to make a new directory mm Lib
制作一个新目录mm Lib
we're gonna put the module modular
我们将把模块模块化
source modular modular versions of the
的源模块模块化版本
Jackson Jackson libraries
杰克逊·杰克逊图书馆
[Music]
[音乐]
Jackson guttacore uses or overrides
Jackson Guttacore使用或覆盖
abductor deprecated API no that's a
绑架者弃用的API否，这是
problem for another day the annotations
问题改天了注解
and data bind bigger module takes a
和数据绑定更大的模块需要一个
little longer to compile ooh more
多一点编译更多
deprecated API okay so now in M Lib
API已弃用，现在在M Lib中
we've got these modular jar files we can
我们有这些模块化的jar文件，我们可以
take a look data vine for example ask
以数据藤为例
the jar tool to describe it and there's
jar工具来描述它，还有
the content of the module declaration in
模块声明中的内容
binary form exports the stuff we
二进制形式导出我们的东西
expected requires the things we expected
期望需要我们期望的东西
we're good to go okay so we've got
我们很好走，所以我们有
modularized Jackson we've got our
模块化的杰克逊，我们有
unmodeled
未建模
tweet some application and let's now try
鸣叫一些应用程序，让我们现在尝试
and run them together so Java module
并一起运行它们，以便Java模块
path M Lib where we put the Jackson
我们将杰克逊放到的路径M Lib
modules class path
模块类路径
well let me just use the
好吧，让我用
tweet some drawer file tweet star Jason
鸣叫一些抽屉文件鸣叫明星杰森
oh yeah there we go
哦，是的，我们走了
okay something went wrong what went
好吧，出了什么问题
wrong well what went wrong was I'm
好吧，哪里出了问题我是
running when you run a class path
运行类路径时运行
application which is what tweets on the
应用程序是什么
tweets um is the model system doesn't
推特um是模型系统不
know what non JDK modules it needs so if
知道需要什么非JDK模块，如果
it needs models outside of the JDK you
它需要JDK之外的模型
need to add them manually so what we'll
需要手动添加它们，以便我们
do is we'll add jackson dot core jackson
我们要做的就是添加杰克逊点芯杰克逊
data mind
数据思维
and Jackson annotations and that works
和杰克逊的注解
so it's a little awkward but at least
所以有点尴尬，但至少
you know this is possible you can have
你知道你有可能
code on the classpath you can have some
在类路径上的代码，你可以有一些
other code in modules on the module path
模块路径上模块中的其他代码
and they work peacefully together but
他们和平共处，
you do have to tell the module system
您必须告诉模块系统
its startup what modules to put in there
它的启动将哪些模块放入其中
so so the the module path is where you
所以模块路径就是你
put artifacts that define modules the ad
放置定义广告模块的工件
what we call sorry the module path is
我们所说的抱歉，模块路径是
where you put your modular drive files
放置模块化驱动器文件的位置
then we have more module jar files that
那么我们有更多的模块jar文件
you want to use rather rather than the
您想使用而不是
clip n on the class path the module
在模块的类路径上剪辑n
system will look on the module path for
系统将在模块路径上查找
modules that it can tell it needs to
它可以告诉它需要的模块
find but when you're just running code
查找，但是当您只运行代码时
on the class path it has no way of
在课堂上，它没有办法
detecting oh this unmod rice code on the
检测哦，这个未修改的大米代码
class path needs some module on the
类路径需要一些模块
module path so add modules tells the
模块路径，因此添加模块告诉
resolver ok to start before you start
可以在开始之前启动解析器
this code on the class path load these
该代码在类路径上加载这些
additional additional modules - plus
其他附加模块-加
whatever modules they depend upon that's
他们所依赖的任何模块
why you need to both use use the module
为什么你们都需要使用模块
path option to say where they are and
指出他们在哪里的路径选项，以及
then the add modules option to say which
然后添加模块选项说出
ones you know are necessary for the code
您知道的代码是必需的
on the class path - if you if you're if
在课程路径上-如果您是
you're in a rush or you just want to be
你很着急或者你只是想成为
lazy there there are there are some
懒惰那里有一些
shortcuts here for example you can say
例如这里的快捷方式，你可以说
all - module path and it will just go
全部-模块路径，它只会走
find everything that's on the module
找到模块上的所有内容
path that's probably not what you want
可能不是您想要的路径
but it can be a useful step if you want
但如果您愿意的话，这可能是一个有用的步骤
to just debug something ok so the way
只是调试好，这样
that this has been bottom-up migration
这是自下而上的迁移
now let's do is kind of the obvious last
现在让我们做的是显而易见的最后
step and modularize everything will go
一步，将一切模块化
back to the tweet some module info which
返回推文中的一些模块信息
I happily left around here will just
我高高兴兴地离开这里会
write it back out and recompile tweet
写回并重新编译tweet
some this time it'll wind up as a
这次有些
modular jar file whoops
模块化jar文件
all right when I compile it now I need
好的，现在编译时我需要
to say tell the compiler module path M
告诉编译器模块路径M
Lib where my actual modules are and
在我实际的模块所在的位置解放
actually going to put tweets um begin to
实际上将把推文开始
end live as well so we are here I have
也要结束，所以我们在这里
an in M Lib all my nice modules and I
在M Lib中，我所有不错的模块和我
can run
能跑
ah where to go now let me just make that
啊，现在要去哪里，我就把那个
again
再次
fully modular greet some applications
全模块化迎接某些应用
now everything is a module we believe we
现在一切都是一个模块，我们相信我们
created a to take them put the top down
创建了一个让他们把顶部放下来
and bottom up everything's a module life
自底向上一切都是模块的生命
is sweet and here we can show a module
很甜，在这里我们可以显示一个模块
resolution and see everything being
分辨率，看到一切
resolved through the route the route is
通过路线解析路线是
the tweets and module as we saw with
我们看到的推文和模块
top-down migration it loads all of these
自上而下的迁移将加载所有这些
other proper modules now they're not
其他适当的模块，现在他们不是
they're not automatic modules anymore
他们不再是自动模块了
and it finishes up by print against
然后通过打印完成
output so that's that's it you know as
输出，就是这样，您就知道
far as far as demonstrating this
就证明这一点而言
migrating to modules does take some work
迁移到模块确实需要一些工作
if you have a large existing system it
如果您现有大型系统，
frankly it might not be worth the effort
坦率地说，这可能不值得
so think carefully before you you start
所以开始之前请三思
off a project and modularize a lot of
一个项目并模块化很多
existing code if you have a large system
现有的代码（如果您使用大型系统）
that's like you know a whole bunch of
就像你知道一大堆
maven projects and it works well and
Maven项目，效果很好，并且
your and and it's kind of in maintenance
您的，并且在维护中
mode
模式
there's a good chance that's not worth
有一个不值得的好机会
going to the trouble of modularizing it
麻烦将其模块化
on the other hand if it's actively
另一方面，如果它是积极的
maintained and evolving and you plan to
保持和发展，您计划
take it forward then it could be worth
推进它，那可能值得
the effort but the good news is jigsaw
努力，但好消息是拼图
provides ways to do both top-down and
提供了自上而下和
bottom-up in my migration when the
自下而上地迁移时
concept of migration is is it's maybe
迁移的概念是
not one of Java's key core values but it
不是Java的关键核心价值之一，而是
definitely ranks up there at something
肯定在某个地方排名靠前
we've we've taken seriously over the
我们已经认真对待了
years it's you know it affected for
年，你知道它影响了
example the design of generics and java
泛型和Java设计示例
5 we took some pains to make sure that
5我们竭尽全力确保
code that adapted to generic types could
适应通用类型的代码可以
work well with code that had not yet
与尚未使用的代码配合使用
been adapted to generic types now by now
现在已适应通用类型
yeah most code does use generic types
是的，大多数代码确实使用泛型类型
but there's still some that doesn't and
但是仍然有一些不
and they all work fine together so we've
他们都一起工作很好，所以我们
taken a similar approach in jigsaw where
在拼图中采取了类似的方法
a code that's in modules and code that's
模块中的代码和
not in modules can coexist and relate to
不在模块中可以共存并与之相关
each other and interoperate
互相合作
so that that is the the concept of
因此，这就是
migration compatibility okay we've got a
迁移兼容性好吧，我们有一个
few minutes left for questions if there
如果有问题还剩几分钟
are any yeah okay plate please wait for
是的，是吗，请等待
the microphone we're the this is being
我们是的麦克风
recorded if you don't wait for the
如果不等待则记录
microphone then it won't be on the
麦克风，那么它就不会在
record Hey
记录嘿
at the beginning you had the Jackson
一开始你有杰克逊
jaws and then you opened up the module
下颚，然后打开模块
and did requires Jackson look before
并要求杰克逊先看
where did that name come from was that
这个名字是从哪里来的
the water magic fun was that an
水魔术的乐趣是
automatic named Ord it was that the
自动命名为Ord是
package name so so when you take it when
包裹名称，所以当你拿的时候
you take a jar file that's that's not
你拿一个不是的jar文件
modular and and and put it on the module
模块化和，并将其放在模块上
path then its module name is synthesized
路径，然后合成其模块名称
from the file name in a way it's a gross
从文件名以某种方式
hack but what else can we do so the name
hack，但我们还能做什么呢？
of the the name of Jack the name of the
杰克的名字
module the automatic model defined by
模块定义的自动模型
Jackson Jackson - cord - 2 dot 6.6 jar
Jackson Jackson-绳-2点6.6罐
is Jackson core and that that's all
是杰克逊的核心，仅此而已
that's all it is it's nothing fancy now
仅此而已
if if the maintainer of that of that
如果那个的维护者
library puts in an automatic module name
库放入一个自动模块名称
entry in the jar files manifest then the
jar文件清单中的条目，然后
name of the automatic module will be
自动模块的名称为
taken from that manifest entry but you
从清单条目中取出，但您
know in the long-term we hope that that
从长远来看，我们希望
any of the libraries like Jackson will
任何像杰克逊这样的图书馆都会
actually be full modules I heard
实际上是我听到的完整模块
recently the the Jackson maintainers
最近杰克逊的维护者
actually did put in the automatic module
实际上确实放入了自动模块
names so they've taken the kind of thing
名字，所以他们采取了那种东西
of the first step down the path to
迈向第一步的第一步
modularizing something
模块化的东西
not any of the I'd say at least free
我不会说至少免费
most common I des that support many of
我最常支持
the commands and tools that you show
您显示的命令和工具
here so so so I had a you Jean Petrenko
在这里，所以所以我有了你Jean Petrenko
from from IntelliJ in the keynote
来自IntelliJ的主题演讲
yesterday demonstrated IntelliJ IDEA it
昨天演示了IntelliJ IDEA
can show module graphs and it has a deep
可以显示模块图，它具有很深的
understanding of how module declarations
了解模块声明的方式
work how they relate to each other if
如果它们之间如何相互联系
you forgot to say require somewhere it
你忘了说某处需要
will suggest insert this one if and and
如果和
and so forth so that so that's pretty
等等，这样很漂亮
slick eclipse has some support but I'm
光滑的日食有一些支持，但我
not sure how deep it is right now I do
不知道现在有多深
know that they're actively working on it
知道他们正在积极努力
and I and I believe the same is true and
我和我都相信这是真的，
that means on that Ben C that means I
这意味着在本C这意味着我
believe the same guy I know net net
相信我认识的那个人
NetBeans contributors are working on
NetBeans贡献者正在努力
them but I don't know the status they
他们，但我不知道他们的状态
haven't released a nine a nine version
还没有发布9 a 9版本
yet haven't released anything in at a
尚未发布任何内容
party right now yeah there's a NetBeans
派对现在是的，有一个NetBeans
there's a nine preview at the moment
目前有九个预览
yeah there is if there's a nine preview
是的，如果有九个预览
but there but it's not it's not final I
但那不是那不是最终的我
think the clips version the supports
认为剪辑版本支持
module two weeks time or well yeah with
模块两个星期的时间还是不错的
it with eclipse there there's a well
有日食的地方
known a well known page on on the
已知的
eclipse website that tells you how to
eclipse网站，告诉您如何
howdy how to use it with nine and their
你好，如何与九人和他们一起使用
formal release will be in a in a few
正式发布将在几
weeks
周
any other questions gentleman in the
先生，还有其他问题吗
back there
回到那里
him hi every current application written
嗨，他写的每个当前申请
in Java 8 will run on a Java 9 virtual
Java 8中的Java将在Java 9虚拟机上运行
machine alright so the quickest answer
机器很好，所以最快的答案
is is referred to free free to the video
是指免费的视频
the keynote for mr. day the more of a
先生的主题演讲。一天更多
slightly more verbose answer is if you
更详细的答案是，如果您
have an existing code that only uses
有一个仅使用的现有代码
Java SE 8 ap is and does not depend on
Java SE 8 AP是并且不依赖于
jdk and journal api's or other internal
JDK和日记API或其他内部
aspects of the jdk people probably work
杰克人的各个方面可能都起作用
on jdk 9 without change thank you I need
在jdk 9上没有变化谢谢你我需要
to show you this slide I work at Oracle
向您展示此幻灯片，我在Oracle工作
hi what's the impact on build tools such
嗨，这对构建工具有什么影响
as maven and Gradle
作为行家和摇篮
well Robert Schulte is sitting right
罗伯特·舒尔特（Robert Schulte）坐好了
here because he could certainly speak he
在这里，因为他当然可以说他
knows a way I know the answer to but
知道我知道答案的方法，但是
there there is impact I'm happy to
有影响，我很高兴
report that we've worked closely with
报告我们已经紧密合作
Robert and and maven has has decent
罗伯特和玛文有体面
support for modules already yes so what
已经支持模块了，那又如何
we did is we tested with maven freedo
我们所做的是我们使用Maven Freedo测试的
and that just works fine probably even
甚至可以正常工作
earlier versions of Mayville all right
Mayville的早期版本可以
also run fine on java 9 but we just
也可以在Java 9上正常运行，但我们只是
started with three or so if there are
从三个左右开始
issues they're often related to the
它们通常与
plugins for instance there was this
例如插件有这个
change to the version scheme where it
更改为版本方案
was one dot and a new version and it has
是一个点和一个新版本，它具有
changed 2.29 and what all these tools
改变了2.29以及所有这些工具
were doing they were making array
在做他们正在做数组
they're splitting it on a dot and taking
他们把它分割成一个点
the second element when it's just nine
第二个元素只有九个
they're getting an array out of mountain
他们从山上走出来
index exception so these are already
索引异常，所以这些已经
fixed and I think most of the plugins
固定，我认为大多数插件
right now are Java now ready so right
现在已经准备好Java了
but but maven also we also will will
但是，行家，我们也会
build modular jar files too now so it's
现在也构建模块化的jar文件，因此
you know it's not just that it that it
你知道这不只是它
works the way it always did online
一直以在线方式运作
it actually has it actually understands
它实际上具有它真正理解的
what modules are and you can have a
什么是模块，您可以拥有一个
module info and do all that stuff
模块信息并完成所有这些工作
just one thing to add you don't have to
只需添加一件事，您就不必
change your folder structure I think
我想改变你的文件夹结构
most of the examples you see that you
您看到的大多数示例中，您
add the module name in a source you
在您添加的源中添加模块名称
don't need that for for major projects
对于大型项目不需要
just keep the source manger up with your
只需跟源管理者保持联系
motivation for there and it will work
那里的动力，它将起作用
right and that that's because pretty
对，那是因为漂亮
much ever and you know a a module is
很多，你知道一个模块是
modules and maven projects are the same
模块和Maven项目相同
thing there are no that we when we're
事情不存在，当我们
showing things on the command line if we
如果我们在命令行显示东西
need to talk about multiple modules than
需要谈论多个模块
we need to show the module the each
我们需要向模块显示每个
module habits have its own directory in
模块习惯在以下位置有其自己的目录
the source path or the moth or the
源路径或飞蛾或
exploded modules but that's just an
爆炸的模块，但这仅仅是一个
artifact really thing is you show Jade
神器真的是你秀玉
EPS
每股收益
in a couple of the slides and Robert has
在几张幻灯片中，罗伯特（Robert）
a plug-in that maven projects can run as
一个可以运行Maven项目的插件
well right good point
好吧，好点
I just wanted to add that we have a
我只是想补充一点，我们有一个
maven buff tonight so if and when it's
今晚的行家buff，所以，如果以及何时
interesting with details we can talk
我们可以谈谈有趣的细节
more until they're excellent any more
直到他们变得更好为止
questions any other questions just a few
质疑其他任何问题
minutes
分钟
over there
在那边
is there any mechanism to versioning
是否有任何版本控制机制
modules no that's frequently asked most
模块不，这是最常被问到的
frequently asked question either number
常见问题解答
one or number two it competes with why
与之竞争的第一或第二
didn't you just fuse osg I know so in
你不只是融合了OSG我知道
this design we took it we took an
这个设计我们接受了
approach it wasn't it was not not our
方法不是不是我们的
original approach we arrived at this
我们到达此的原始方法
after after a long time an approach
经过很长一段时间后
where modules and the artifacts that
模块和工件的位置
define them are separate concepts so a
定义它们是独立的概念，因此
module is is is kind of a higher level
模块是更高级别的一种
abstraction they're embedded in the
它们嵌入在
language they're known to the virtual
虚拟人所熟悉的语言
machine
机
they don't have version numbers in that
他们没有版本号
environment you know things thing the
环境你知道的东西
module is you know is as fundamental as
你知道模块是最基本的
a class or an interface we don't put
我们不放置的类或接口
versions on those but we do put versions
这些版本，但我们确实放版本
on the things that contain them so it
在包含它们的东西上
makes perfect sense to have versions on
拥有版本非常合理
a modular jar file and but we basically
模块化的jar文件，但是我们基本上
leave it to build tools like maven and
留下来构建诸如maven和
Gradle an ant whatever to worry about
让一只蚂蚁摇摇欲坠
version conflicts the module system will
版本冲突模块系统将
detect conflicts if you have two modular
如果有两个模块化，则检测冲突
jar files in the same directory on the
jar文件位于
module path that define models of the
定义模型的模块路径
same name the module system will just
模块系统将使用相同的名称
stop and say I it doesn't know how to
停下来说我不知道​​该怎么做
make this choice so you have to remove
做出选择，所以您必须删除
one of them or fix the problem modules
其中之一或修复问题模块
do have this art we compiled modules
确实有这种艺术，我们编译了模块
can't have module information in them if
如果其中没有模块信息
I if I list modules you see this this at
如果我列出模块，您会在
9 you know that 9 is inserted by you
9您知道您插入了9
know by the build system into the module
由构建系统知道进入模块
info dot class files but it's just there
信息点类文件，但是就在那里
as documentation so that that version
作为文档，以便该版本
string is is not really interpreted it's
字符串不是真的被解释为
just carried through for diagnosis so if
只是进行诊断，所以如果
you're trying to diagnose something
您正在尝试诊断某些东西
wrong in a large system you can see
在大型系统中您可以看到错误
which versions of modules were resolved
解决了哪些版本的模块
but the resolver doesn't actually pay
但解析器实际上并没有付款
attention to those version strings
注意那些版本字符串
you know as I said it is a little bit of
就像我说的那样，你知道
a counterintuitive approach which is why
违反直觉的方法，这就是为什么
people naturally ask about it a lot but
人们自然会问很多，但是
that's the answer and you know sorry so
这就是答案，您知道抱歉
far this seems to be working fairly well
到目前为止，这似乎工作得很好
further
进一步
well alright time for maybe one more
好的时间也许还有一个
okay well thank you very much
好的，非常感谢你
go forth and modular eyes
往前走，模块化的眼睛
[Applause]
[掌声]